ACTWU's Research Department Company Records 5619/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Rural Retreat Garment Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 73)
- Russell's Formal Wear, Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 74)
  Toledo, OH
- Rutgers Coat Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 75)
- Ryder Truck Rental, Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 76)
  Bloomington, IL
- Ryt-Way Packaging Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 91, Folder 77)
  Northfield, MN
- S & M Alpine International, Inc., 1983 (Box 91, Folder 78)
- S.M.K., Inc., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 79)
- SMS Textile Mills, Inc., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 80)
- S & S Fashions, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 81)
- S W S Garment, Inc., 1983 (Box 91, Folder 82)
- Sacks Textile Associates, Inc., 1983 (Box 91, Folder 83)
  Clark, NJ
- Allyn St. George, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 84)
- St. Joseph's Hospital, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 85)
- Safety Apparel Industries, Inc., 1981 (Box 91, Folder 86)
- Saint Laurie Ltd., 1973-1992 (Box 91, Folder 87)
- Samit Fashions Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 88)
- Samco, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 89)
  Galax, VA
- Samtex Dyeing and Finishing Corporation, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 90)
- San Joaquin Industries, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 91)
- Sander Consumer Products Corporation, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 92)
  Cohoes, NY
- Sasser Electric & Manufacturing Co., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 93)
  Mount Hope, WV
- Samson Ocean Systems, Inc., 1970-1983 (Box 91, Folder 94)
  Icard, NC; Newspaper Clipping Included
- San Val, Inc., 1983 (Box 91, Folder 95)
  Steelville, MO
- Sasson Brothers Embroidery Corporation, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 96)
- Sattler's, Inc., 1968-1982 (Box 91, Folder 97)
- Saucony Shoe Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 98)
  See also: Hyde Athletic Industries, Inc.; Macungie, PA
- Savin Corporation, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 99)
  Anaheim, CA; Newspaper Article Photocopy Included
- Savoy Leather Manufacturing Corporation, 1979-1983 (Box 91, Folder 100)
  Haverhill, MA
- Frank Sbicca and Company, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 91, Folder 101)
- Schneider Inc., 1982 (Box 91, Folder 102)
- School House Candy Co., 1980 (Box 91, Folder 103)
  Pawtucket, RI
- Irwin B. Schwabe Company, Inc., 1958-1981 (Box 91, Folder 104)
- SCOA Industries, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 91, Folder 105)
  Columbus, OH; 1978 annual Report Included
- Schreter Industries, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 106)
- Scottdale Mills, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 107)
  Scottdale, GA
- The Scranton Corporation, 1975-1983 (Box 91, Folder 108)
  See also: Scranton Lace Co.; Scranton, PA
- Scully Rubber Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 91, Folder 109)
- Searle Medical Products USA, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  Ozark, AL
- Sedgefield Sportswear, 1974-1982 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  Division of Blue Bell, Inc.; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies
- Selmer Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  Selmer, TN
- Seminole Manufacturing Co., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  Newspaper Clipping; New York, NY
- The Selvin Shoe Company, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Serac, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  Sandpoint, ID; Formerly Seattle, WA; Newspaper Clipping
- M. Setlow & Son, Inc., 1960-1983 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Seven Star Shoe, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Sew Nice Togs, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Shaer Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  Manchester, NH; 1980 annual Report Included
- Shalom Manufacturing Co., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  Santurce, PR
- Shamrock Packaging, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  Totowa, NJ
- Shapely, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- She Shop, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  Bohemia, NY
- Shedrain Corporation, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  Portland, OR; Newspaper Article Photocopy
- Sheltex Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  Brewton, AL
- Shenandoah Valley Press, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Ship 'N Shore, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Shoes By Edward Dorf, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Shutzer Enterprises, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Shutzer Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963-1983 (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Signal Thread Co., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 22)
- Sikes Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  Rome, GA; 1981 Annual Report Included
- Simplex Industries Inc., 1971-1980 (Box 92, Folder 24)
- Simtex Yarns, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  See also: Marlboro Shirt Co.
- The Singer Co., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 26)
- Howe K. Sipes Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 27)
- Slaks Fifth Avenue, 1981-1983 (Box 92, Folder 28)
- Slater Dye Works, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 92, Folder 29)
- Slater Screen Print Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 30)
- Slazenger, Ltd., 1975-1983 (Box 92, Folder 31)
- Sleepwear, Inc., 1963-1980 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  See also: SouthPine Nightwear Co.; York, PA; Newspaper Article Photocopy Included
- Slocomb Apparel, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 33)
- Smead Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  Logan, OH
- Sobel, Bernstein & Greene Shoe Co., Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  Newspaper Article Photocopy Included; Los Angeles, CA
- Solidarity Workers Wear, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 36)
- Soloray Knitting, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  Division of Sunbeam Corporation
- M. Soman Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 38)
- Sono-Therm, Inc., 1971-1983 (Box 92, Folder 39)
- Southeastern Sportswear, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 40)
- Southern Felt Co., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  Newspaper Clipping; Clinton, SC
- Southern Silk Mills, Inc., 1977-1981 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Spring City, TN
- Southern Worsted Mills, Inc., 1972-1980 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  Newspaper Clippings; Greenville, SC
- Sparkle Togs, Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 44)
- Sphinx Packaging Corporation, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 45)
  Millington, NJ
- Spinlon Industries, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 46)
  Quakertown, PA
- Sportco, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 47)
- Sportee Corporation of North Carolina, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 48)
  Subsidiary Of Famous Cotton, Inc.
- Sporto Corporation, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 49)
  Magazine Article Photocopy Included
- Spray-O-Matic Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 50)
- Springdale Canada, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 51)
- Springs Industries, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 92, Folder 52)
  Research Project 1980
- Stacy Fabrics Corporation, 1975-1983 (Box 92, Folder 53)
  Newspaper Clipping Included; Passaic, NJ
- Standard Coat, Apron & Linen Service, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 54)
- Standard Dyeing & Finishing Co., 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 55)
  Paterson, NJ; Newspaper Article Photocopies Included
- Standard Oil Company. Indiana, 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 56)
  1979 Annual Report Included
- Star Sportswear Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1970-1982 (Box 92, Folder 57)
- State Bank of Albany, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 58)
  Albany, NY
- State Of The Art Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 59)
- State Machine Products, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 60)
  Dry Ridge, KY
- Steelcase, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 61)
  Fletcher, NC
- Steinthal Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 62)
- Stelwood, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 63)
- Stem Industries, Inc., 1974-1981 (Box 92, Folder 64)
  Atlanta, GA; 1974 annual Report Included
- Star Textile & Research Inc., 1970-1982 (Box 92, Folder 65)
- Stephens, W.E. Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 66)
- Edmond Stern Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 67)
- Michael Stern & Co., Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 92, Folder 68)
- Stevens Linen Associates, 1981-1984 (Box 92, Folder 69)
  Webster, MA; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies
- Steven Wayne Knitting Mills, Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 70)
- Stewart Group Ltd., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 71)
- D. Stone Industries, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 72)
- Stoneham & Rutters Laundry, Inc., 1978-1980 (Box 92, Folder 73)
  Lawrence, MA; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Stoneham Laundry, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 92, Folder 74)
- Storey, W.R. Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 75)
- William Stuart Industries, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 76)
- Styl-Land, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 77)
- Style Master Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 78)
- Sue & Sam Co., Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 92, Folder 79)
- Sunbury Textile Mills, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 92, Folder 80)
  Sunbury, PA; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- A. Sulka & Sons, 1958-1980 (Box 92, Folder 81)
  Peerless Shirt Co.; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies
- Sullcraft Manufacturing Co., 1968-1983 (Box 92, Folder 82)
- Summit Nursing Home, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 83)
  Lakewood, NJ
- Sunset Plastic Products, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 84)
  Shawnee Mission, KS
- Surrey Industries, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 85)
  Allentown, PA; Newspaper Article Photocopies Included
- Susan Garment Co., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 86)
- Susan Shoe Industries, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 87)
- Sutton & Sutton Ltd., 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 88)
- Sutton Shirt Co., 1968-1982 (Box 92, Folder 89)
  Division of Spartans Industries; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- Swainsboro Print Works, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 90)
- Syms Haberdashery, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 91)
- Sweetwater Carpet Corporation, 1979-1982 (Box 92, Folder 92)
  Ringgold, GA; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Sweet Candy Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 93)
  Salt Lake City, UT
- TKG International Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 94)
- TMC Industries, Ltd. [Folder 1 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 92, Folder 95)
  See also: WWG Industries, Inc.
- TMC Industries, Ltd. [Folder 2 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 92, Folder 96)
- Tabb Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 97)
- Taighmore Sportswear, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 98)
- Talco Sportswear, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 99)
- E.H. Taliaferro Manufacturing Co., 1967-1982 (Box 92, Folder 100)
- Taverly Inc., 1974-1982 (Box 92, Folder 101)
- Tavern Owners Products Co., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 102)
- Taylor Co., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 103)
- Technical Investments, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 104)
  Berryville, AK
- Technital, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 105)
  Clifton, NJ
- Technofil Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 106)
- Tempo Togs Ltd. Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 107)
- Tennessee American Products, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 108)
- Tennessee Meat Producers, Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 109)
  Maryville, TN
- Terry Lee Sportswear, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 110)
  Union City, NJ
- Textron, Inc., 1963-1981 (Box 92, Folder 111)
  Providence, RI
- Thermal Industries, Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 112)
- Thiokol Chemical Corporation, 1970-1980 (Box 92, Folder 113)
  Thiokol Fibers Division; See also: Wayn-Tex, Inc.; Waynesboro, VA; Newspaper Clipping and Photocopies Included
- P.J. Thompson & Co., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 114)
- Thorpe Weaving, Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 92, Folder 115)
  Zaleschitz Mills, Inc.; Jim Thorpe, PA
- Three Guy Laroche, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 116)
- Tiara Coat Fashions, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 117)
- Tietex Fibers, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 92, Folder 118)
- Tifton Textiles, Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 119)
  Tifton, GA
- Tilton Rack & Basket Manufacturing Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 120)
  Fairfield, NJ
- Timex Corporation, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 121)
  Middlebury, CT
- Tiny Tots Knitting Mills, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 122)
- Tolaram Fibers, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 123)
- Toledo Mattress Company, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 124)
- Toledo Optical Laboratory, Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 125)
- Tom & Huck Togs, Inc., 1965-1982 (Box 92, Folder 126)
- Tonka Footwear Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 127)
- Top Co., 1974-1983 (Box 92, Folder 128)
  South Barre, MA; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Topat Sportswear, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 129)
- Torrington Co., 1968-1981 (Box 92, Folder 130)
  Syracuse, NY; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Town & Country Mobile Homes, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 131)
- Town & Country Department Stores, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 132)
- Town & Country Rainwear Inc., 1983-1988 (Box 92, Folder 133)
- Toyobo Co., of Osaka. Japan, 1967-1980 (Box 92, Folder 134)
- E. Trani & Son Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 135)
- Transco Textile Industry, Ltd., 1973-1980 (Box 92, Folder 136)
  Augusta, GA; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Trappings (Box 92, Folder 137)
- Tred Z Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 138)
- Tred 2, Inc., 1980 (Box 92, Folder 139)
- The Trend Group Ltd., Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 140)
- A Trifle Bit, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 141)
- Tri-H Corporation, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 142)
- Tri-State Envelope Corporation, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 143)
  Ashland, PA
- Tri-State Paper Box Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 144)
  Middletown, NY
- Trissi Inc., 1973-1982 (Box 92, Folder 145)
- Troya Footwear, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 146)
- Tubbs Cordage Co., 1976-1982 (Box 92, Folder 147)
  Jackson Rope Division; Austin, TX
- Turn-A-Round Ltd., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 148)
- Tweave Inc., 1982 (Box 92, Folder 149)
- Twin City Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966 (Box 92, Folder 150)
- Uro Weaving Inc., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 151)
- U.S. Apparel, Inc., 1981 (Box 92, Folder 152)
- U.S. Dye Works, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 153)
- U.S. High Pile Knitting Corporation, 1969-1980 (Box 92, Folder 154)
- U.S. Wiping Cloth, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 155)
- Ungerer & Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- United Canvas & Sling, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  Hackensack, NJ; Newspaper Clipping
- United Fashion Industries, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Universal Converting Corporation (Box 93, Folder 4)
  New Bedford, MA
- Universal Rundle Corporation, 1983-1987 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  Corsicana, TX; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Uptown Clothes, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Upwear Corporation, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Utility Equipment Company, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Vagden Mills Ltd., 1968-1981 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  Toronto and Belleville, Ontario; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Valley Apparel, Inc., 1981 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  Strasburg, VA
- Value City Corporation, 1980-1984 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  Columbus, OH; Newspaper Article Photocopy Included
- Van Dorn Company, 1973-1981 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  Cleveland, OH; 1981 annual Report Included
- Vanier Graphics, 1982-1983 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  Subsidiary Of American Business Products, Inc.; Eden, NC
- Vaughan-Bassett Furniture Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Vermont Sportswear, Inc., 1967-1982 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Vestra Union Clothing Corporation, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Vibra Screw Incorporated, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Viceroy Sportswear, Inc., 1975-1981 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Victory Shirt Co., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Viking Machine Co., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Vimar Footwear, Inc., 1981 (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Vi-Mill, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 22)
- Vi-Mo Manufacturing Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Vinaflex of America, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 24)
- Viner Brothers, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 25)
- Virginia Products Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 26)
- Virginia Miss, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 27)
- Vita Shoe Corporation, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 28)
- Vornado, 1967-1980 (Box 93, Folder 29)
- W & G Products Company Inc., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 30)
- W & J Co., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 31)
- WDH Co., 1981 (Box 93, Folder 32)
- WWG Industries, Inc., 1970-1996 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  Roxbury Carpet Division; Chattanooga, TN; See also: TMC Industries, Inc.; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Wadsworth-Greenwood Corporation, 1973-1980 (Box 93, Folder 34)
- Wakefield Leathers, Inc., 1966 (Box 93, Folder 35)
- Walkin Shoe Co., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 36)
  Schuylkill Haven, PA
- Walter Carpet Mills, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 37)
- Waltham Shirt Co., Inc., 1964-1982 (Box 93, Folder 38)
- Walton Manufacturing Company Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 39)
- Warner Amex Cable Communication, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 40)
- Warren Industries, Inc., 1964 (Box 93, Folder 41)
  Glens Falls, NY
- Warsaw Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1981 (Box 93, Folder 42)
- Water Valley Manufacturing Co., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 43)
- Waterbury Mattress Co., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 44)
- Waynesboro Garment Co., 1957-1983 (Box 93, Folder 45)
- Waynesboro Knitting Co., Inc., 1961-1983 (Box 93, Folder 46)
- Weather Vane Outerwear Corporation, 1969-1980 (Box 93, Folder 47)
- Weave Corporation, 1980-1984 (Box 93, Folder 48)
  Hackensack, NJ; Magazine Article Included
- Webster Locksmith, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 49)
- Wee Girls, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 50)
- Weintraub, George & Sons, Inc., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 51)
- Weldon Inc., 1965-1981 (Box 93, Folder 52)
- Welpro, Inc., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 53)
- Wendell Textiles Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 54)
- Wesco Fabrics Inc., 1981 (Box 93, Folder 55)
- West Bay Design, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 56)
- Western Pacific Industries, Inc., 1980 (Box 93, Folder 57)
- Western Union Corporation, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 58)
- Western Yarns, Inc., 1974-1997 (Box 93, Folder 59)
  Commerce, CA
- Westover Knitting Mills, Inc., 1970-1982 (Box 93, Folder 60)
  Indian Orchard, MA; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Wexler Knitting Mills, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 61)
- Wex-Tex of Ashford, Inc., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 62)
- Whiffle Tree Hill Golf Course, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 63)
- Whirlaway Textile Spindles, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 64)
  Wellington, OH
- Fred Whitaker Co., Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 65)
  Roanoke, VA
- White Mountain Industries, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 66)
- Whitehall Electro-Medical Corporation, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 67)
- Whittaker Corporation, 1967-1982 (Box 93, Folder 68)
  Newspaper Clippings Included; Los Angeles, CA
- Whittaker Corporation, 1971-1983 (Box 93, Folder 69)
  Thermo Plastic Corp. Subsidiary; Pinesville, NC; 1982 Annual Report Included; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Wiebel Associates, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 70)
  Sussex, NJ
- WWG Industries, Inc., 1969-1983 (Box 93, Folder 71)
  Trend Carpet Division; Rome, GA; Newspaper Clippings Included
- M. Wile & Co., 1942-1983 (Box 93, Folder 72)
- Wilgree Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 93, Folder 73)
  Wilk Shirt Corporation
- Will Ross, Inc. Financial & General, 1973-1981 (Box 93, Folder 74)
- Will Ross, Inc. White Knight Division, 1971-1983 (Box 93, Folder 75)
- Willcox & Gibbs Inc., 1967-1983 (Box 93, Folder 76)
  1974 Annual Report Included; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Wilshire, Inc., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 77)
- Thomas Wilson & Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 78)
- Wilton Enterprises, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 93, Folder 79)
- Windsor Knit Co., Inc., 1979 (Box 93, Folder 80)
- Winfield Manufacturing Corporation [Folder 1 of 2], 1961-1983 (Box 93, Folder 81)
  Belmont, MS
- Winfield Manufacturing Corporation [Folder 2 of 2], 1961-1983 (Box 93, Folder 82)
- Winners Circle Fashions, Inc., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 83)
- Winston Uniform Corporation, 1966-1981 (Box 93, Folder 84)
- Jack Winter Manufacturing Corporation, 1961-1969 (Box 93, Folder 85)
  Marianna, AR
- Wisconsin/Louis Spero Co., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 86)
- Wood-Way Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 93, Folder 87)
  Shelbyville, TN; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Woolco Department Stores, 1969-1984 (Box 93, Folder 88)
- Worcester Knitting Co., Inc., 1960-1983 (Box 93, Folder 89)
  Cherry Valley, MA
- Wright, E.T. & Co., Inc., 1982 (Box 93, Folder 90)
- Wyomissing Corporation, 1971-1983 (Box 93, Folder 91)
- X.M.I. Corporation, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 92)
- York Narrow Fabrics Co., 1973-1980 (Box 93, Folder 93)
- Yves St. Laurent Men's Clothing, 1968-1982 (Box 93, Folder 94)
- Zale Corporation, 1966-1982 (Box 93, Folder 95)
- Zeda Holdings, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 96)
- Zeyno Group-America Ltd., 1983 (Box 93, Folder 97)
- Zimco Industries, Inc., 1973-1981 (Box 93, Folder 98)
- A & K Knitting Mills, Inc., 1986 (Box 93, Folder 99)
- A & R Pet Food Co., Inc., 1985 (Box 93, Folder 100)
- A & Z Apparel, Inc., 1984 (Box 93, Folder 101)
- AKY Hat Corporation, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 102)
- AMCA International, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 103)
- AMF, Inc., 1978-1988 (Box 93, Folder 104)
- AMF, Inc., 1975-1987 (Box 93, Folder 105)
  Division of Head Sportswear; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies
- AMP-CET, Inc., 1984 (Box 93, Folder 106)
- A.Q. Industries, Inc., 1986 (Box 93, Folder 107)
- ASL Industries, Inc., 1980-1986 (Box 93, Folder 108)
  Subsidiary Of Alpine Group, Inc.
- Abbott Laboratories, 1973-1985 (Box 93, Folder 109)
- Abney Mills, 1971-1984 (Box 93, Folder 110)
- Absecon Mills, Inc., 1986 (Box 93, Folder 111)
- Active Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1985 (Box 93, Folder 112)
  Plainfield, CT
- Addison Shoe Co., 1979-1984 (Box 93, Folder 113)
  See also: Munro & Co.; Newspaper Article Photocopies Included
- Adelaide Mills, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 114)
  Anniston, AL; Newspaper article Photocopy Included
- Adirondack Leather Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 93, Folder 115)
- Admor, Inc., 1985 (Box 93, Folder 116)
- Ad-Mart Attractions, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Ad-Rite Co., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Advanced Window Corporation, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Affiliated Hospital Products, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- AKY Hat Corporation, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Albrizio Inc., 1985 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Aldo Hat Corporation, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Algro Knitting Mills, Inc., 1970-1984 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  Milltown, NJ
- Allegheny Knitting Mills, Inc., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Allen Co., 1986 (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Allen Sportswear Corporation, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Allesons of Rochester Inc., 1970-1981 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Allied Products Corporation, 1965-1983 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  Fabrics America, Inc., Division; Enterprise, AL; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included
- Allied Stores-Campeau Corporation, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 14)
- Allied Stores Corporation, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  J.B. Hunter; Newspaper Article Photocopy
- Allison Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1963-1984 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  See also: Manchester Knitted Fashions; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Alloy Steel Tank & Welding Co., 1986 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Allstate Lawn Products, Inc., 1977-1984 (Box 94, Folder 18)
- Altoona Mattress Co., 1985 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  Altoona, PA
- Amcest Corporation, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  Roselle, NJ; Newspaper Clipping Included
- Amerace Corporation, 1976-1984 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  1976 Annual Report Included
- Amerex of California, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- American Business Products, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  Vanier Graphics Corporation, Subsidiary; 1982-1983 Annual Reports Included; Newspaper Article Photocopies Included
- American Cellophane & Plastics, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- American Electric Cordsets Co., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  Bensenville, IL
- American Fiber & Finishing, Inc., 1986 (Box 94, Folder 26)
- American Hospital Supply Corporation, 1972-1985 (Box 94, Folder 27)
- American Packaging Corporation, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 28)
- American Recreation Group, 1978-1984 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  Limited Partnership
- American Silk Mills Corporation, 1979-1986 (Box 94, Folder 30)
- American Southern Textile Co., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 31)
- American Spinning Industries, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  Central Falls, RI; Article Photocopy
- American Thread Co., 1976-1985 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  Willimantic, CT; Negotiations, 1976; Newspaper Clippings and Photocopies Included; 1977-1979 Annual Reports Included
- Amertex Enterprises Ltd., Inc., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 34)
- Amity Leather Products Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  Albuquerque, NM
- Apparelcraft Associates, Inc., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 36)
- Applikay Textile Processing Corporation, 1975-1984 (Box 94, Folder 37)
  Passaic, NJ; Newspaper Clippings
- Argus Brands, 1969-1986 (Box 94, Folder 38)
- Arian Fashions, Inc., 1984 (Box 94, Folder 39)
- Ashworth Brothers, Inc., 1972-1984 (Box 94, Folder 40)
  Fall River, MA; Also Plants in SC, NC, GA, & Canada; Newspaper Clippings Included
- Asten Group, Inc., 1970-1985 (Box 94, Folder 41)
  Formerly: Asten-Hill Manufacturing Co.; Walterboro, SC
- Astor Corporation, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 42)
  Portland, ME
- Athearn, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 43)
- Atlantic Chemical Corporation, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 44)
- Austin Reed Group, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 45)
  Subsidiary Of Austin Reed & Chester Barrie; Newspaper Clipping
- Avalon Industries, Inc., 1985 (Box 94, Folder 46)
- B & B Co., 1971-1984 (Box 94, Folder 47)